{
    "id": "4ff5781560e1458197f46903b3727c09",
    "title": "Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Don’t call them now. They ………………….. have gone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "can",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Could I ask you something?’ ‘Yes, of course you …………………..’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Where is Sarah?’ ‘She ………………………. have gone swimming.’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "............................................. you smoke in public spaces?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Can",
                "May"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Yesterday evening, I ........................................ watch TV for an hour.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "could",
                "was allowed to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We …………………. go camping this summer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "may"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You ..................................... worry about the consequences.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "don't must",
                "must not"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": ".......................................... you have some more potatoes?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Can",
                "Shall"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "British people .......................................... get a visa to go to Scotland.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must not",
                "don't need to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I couldn’t think properly. Perhaps I …………………. Ill.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "might be"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}